fourweekmba.com 2019-06-16

# Cookies, Privacy and GDPR Policy Page - FourWeekMBA

## **Cookies**

To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.

## **What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size, and other display preferences) over some time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. 

## **How do we use cookies?**

_This site is hosted by WordPress.com, and as such it  _makes use of cookies for a variety of different purposes. These include those that are ‘strictly necessary’ for technical reasons; those that enable a personalized experience for visitors and registered users; and those that allow the display of advertising from selected third party networks. Some of these cookies may be set when a page is loaded, or when a visitor takes a particular action, such as clicking the ‘like’ or ‘follow’ button on a post.

To have a complete overview, you can consult the [WordPress.com Cookie Page](https://en.support.wordpress.com/cookies/).

## **ABOUT COOKIES & LOG FILES**

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gather limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, the operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your account password, so you do not have to sign in every time you visit your account page.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

### GOOGLE COOKIES

WordLift uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use using cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information.

Google’s privacy policy is available at <https://policies.google.com/privacy>.

## **How to control cookies**

You can **control and delete** cookies as you wish – for details, see [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer, and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site, and some services and functionalities may not work.

## **GDPR Compliance**

On this site, there is no processing of sensible users’ data (credit cards, personal information). The best effort is made to emphasize the privacy of users on this platform.

## What personal data do we collect?

The primary data we collect is your email, under your consent through forms, pop-ups, and integrations. We do that so you can take part in this business community and receive updates on the most interesting stuff we have to offer you.

We use your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and with your Consent.

On the grounds of entering into a contract or fulfilling contractual obligations, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * To identify you for communication purposes
  * To provide you a service or to send/offer you a product

With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * To send you newsletters and campaign offers (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);
  * For other purposes we have asked your consent for;

We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.

We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience. We share your data with:
